<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>autoscaling on Kurt Madel</title>
    <link>https://kurtmadel.com/tags/autoscaling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in autoscaling on Kurt Madel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2019 Kurt Madel All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 07:23:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kurtmadel.com/tags/autoscaling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just-in-Time Autoscaling for Jenkins Agents with Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/just-in-time-autoscaling-for-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 07:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/just-in-time-autoscaling-for-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>In Part 2 of the series CI/CD on Kubernetes we set up cluster autoscaling for a dedicated Jenkins agent node pool by utilizing the PodNodeSelector and LimitRanger admission controllers. In Part 3 of this CI/CD on Kubernetes series we will take advantage of another admission controller to scale-up the Jenkins agents node pool before a new request for a Jenkins agent pod requires the additional capacity. In other words, we want to initiate scaling-up of the Jenkins agent node pool before it is actually needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autoscaling Jenkins Agents with Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/autoscaling-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 23:09:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/autoscaling-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>In Part 1 of the series CI/CD on Kubernetes we used the PodNodeSelector admission controller to segregate the Jenkins workloads - agents from masters (and from any other workload running on the cluster). In Part 2 of this CI/CD on Kubernetes series we will utilize the segregated jenkins-agents node pool as part of an autoscaling solution for the Jenkins agent workload, without impacting the availability or performance of the Jenkins masters node pool or any other segregated workload on the cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>