<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kurt Madel</title>
    <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kurt Madel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2019 Kurt Madel All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 21:00:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kurtmadel.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tekton Pipelines: Standardizing Native Kubernetes Continuous Delivery</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/native-kubernetes-continuous-delivery/tekton-standardizing-native-kubernetes-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 21:00:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/native-kubernetes-continuous-delivery/tekton-standardizing-native-kubernetes-cd/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most exciting project that was announced as one of the four initial Continuous Delivery Foundation (CDF) projects is Tekton Pipelines, which in the vein of the Kubernetes ecosystem naming conventions is from the Ancient Greek word for carpenter. It is also the youngest of the four initial CDF projects. Surrounded by industry stalwarts with Jenkins on one side and Spinnaker the other - and then there is the upstart Jenkins X that is just over a year old, but seems much much older in tech years compared to Tekton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 26, 1993</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/9-26-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 09:32:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/9-26-93/</guid>
      <description>9-26-93 I am once again an inhabitant of Camp Schwab. My Company returned late on the night of the 23rd, and has now settled in quite nicely to the way things went prior to Fuji. Of course things are never EXACTLY the same. OurThe commanding officer of our company has initiated his very own personally modified United States Marine Corps Dress Code. By order of Capt G.A. Uribe, all personnel in Co F, 2nd Bn, 4th Mar will at all time except when PTing or in the barracks, wear a collared shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 11, 1993</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/9-11-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 22:45:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/9-11-93/</guid>
      <description>9-11-93 Never did finish reading &amp;lsquo;Moby Dick&amp;rsquo;. Melville&amp;rsquo;s vernacular might as well be Japanese. Rather than try to figure out Herman&amp;rsquo;s enigmatic language, I went for the easy thrill by reading John Grisham&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;The Pelican Brief&amp;rsquo;. Nothing too deep, but entertaining never the less. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s a best seller and Melville died poor. The general public likes the easy thrill, an easy break from the rat race. I lost my frame of thought because I had to shit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 21 &amp; 22, 1993</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/2-21-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 21:29:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/2-21-93/</guid>
      <description>2-21-93 Last night I drank some pretty rough 190 proof alcohol, to what point I&amp;rsquo;m not exactly certain. Basically just to get obliterated and loose my mind; and as an extra, to wake up with the hangover that doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to go away.
Found out that we&amp;rsquo;re leaving CAX on the 23rd, hopefully late. If it&amp;rsquo;s late, then that means an extremely short work week, with a 96 starting on the 25th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 3, 1993</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/3-3-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 12:03:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/incoherent-thoughts-of-a-young-marine/3-3-93/</guid>
      <description>3-3-93 That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of threes, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you say. Not more than three weeks ago, I told myself, &amp;ldquo;Kurt, things are going to change. You are going to start being a doer, and not just a dreamer.&amp;rdquo; Everybody dreams, but few do. It feels funky, wrong, bad being a secretary with fervent military interests. Sitting on one&amp;rsquo;s ass all day sap&amp;rsquo;s the mollasses right out of you. A good day needs to be balanced between mental &amp;amp; physical / subjective &amp;amp; objective activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just-in-Time Autoscaling for Jenkins Agents with Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/just-in-time-autoscaling-for-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 07:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/just-in-time-autoscaling-for-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>In Part 2 of the series CI/CD on Kubernetes we set up cluster autoscaling for a dedicated Jenkins agent node pool by utilizing the PodNodeSelector and LimitRanger admission controllers. In Part 3 of this CI/CD on Kubernetes series we will take advantage of another admission controller to scale-up the Jenkins agents node pool before a new request for a Jenkins agent pod requires the additional capacity. In other words, we want to initiate scaling-up of the Jenkins agent node pool before it is actually needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autoscaling Jenkins Agents with Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/autoscaling-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 23:09:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/autoscaling-jenkins-agents-with-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>In Part 1 of the series CI/CD on Kubernetes we used the PodNodeSelector admission controller to segregate the Jenkins workloads - agents from masters (and from any other workload running on the cluster). In Part 2 of this CI/CD on Kubernetes series we will utilize the segregated jenkins-agents node pool as part of an autoscaling solution for the Jenkins agent workload, without impacting the availability or performance of the Jenkins masters node pool or any other segregated workload on the cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Segregating Jenkins Agents on Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/segregating-jenkins-agents-on-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:49:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kurtmadel.com/posts/cicd-with-kubernetes/segregating-jenkins-agents-on-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>This is the first part in the series CI/CD on Kubernetes. In this part we will explore the use of Kubernetes Namespaces and the Kubernetes PodNodeSelector Admission Controller to segregate Jenkins agent workloads from the Jenkins server (or master) workloads - as well as other workloads on the Kubernetes cluster. As we continue on with the series we will see why this will serve as an important foundation for managing Kubernetes configuration for Jenkins agent related features such as autoscaling, resource quotas and security constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>